https://www.proboatclean.com/privacy-cookies-policy/

XHomeServicesGalleryLocationsAbout Us Service GuaranteeEnvironmentFAQsEnquiryTestimonials
Privacy & Cookies PolicyOVERVIEWOur commitment is to put our customers and site users first. We strive to:Be transparent about how we collect and use your information.Keep your information secure.Provide you with meaningful choices.This Privacy Policy is intended to help you understand what information Pro Boat Clean collects:During the course of your use of our website proboatclean.com.During the course of any interaction with our social media accounts.When you interact with us either online via email marketing or at events.Why we collect your data and what we do with it.Last updated 18th October 2018.WHAT DATA DO WE COLLECTPersonal data means any information capable of identifying an individual. It does not include anonymised data.We may process certain types of personal data about you as follows:Identity Data – may include your first name, last name, username.
Contact Data – may include your billing address, email address and telephone numbers.
Financial Data – may include your bank account details.
Transaction Data – may include details about payments between us and other details of purchases made by you.
Technical Data – may include your login data, internet protocol addresses, browser type and version, browser plug-in types and versions, time zone setting and location, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this site.
Profile Data – may include your username and password, purchases or orders.
Usage Data – may include information about how you use our website, products and services.
Marketing and Communications Data – may include your preferences in receiving marketing communications from us and your communication preferences.We may also process Aggregated Data from your personal data but this data does not reveal your identity and as such in itself is not personal data. An example of this is where we review your Website Usage Data to work out the most popular sections in our site.HOW WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATADirect interactions: You may provide data by filling in forms on our site (or otherwise) or by communicating with us by post, phone, email or otherwise, including when you:Order our products or services.Create an account on our site.Subscribe to our service or publications.Request resources or marketing be sent to you.Enter a competition, prize draw, promotion or survey or give us feedback.Sign up for a newsletter or use our contact form.Automated technologies or interactions: As you use our site, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and usage patterns. We collect this data by using cookies, server logs and similar technologies. We may also receive Technical Data about you if you visit other websites that use our cookies.Events/Interactions: You may provide your data at an event or you may provide us with your details during a meeting or conference. This data is treated securely from the moment of receiving and transferred to our secure online data software during or directly after the event or meeting.HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATAWe will only use your personal data when legally permitted. The most common uses of your personal data are:Where we need to perform the contract between us.Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.Generally, we do not rely on consent as a legal ground for processing your personal data, other than in relation to sending marketing communications to you via email.NOTE: You have the right to withdraw consent to marketing at any time by emailing us at unsubscribing from our email communications or amending your data on our website on this link.PURPOSES FOR PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL DATAWe may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground, depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please contact us if you require further information.MARKETING COMMUNICATIONSYou will receive marketing communications from us if you have:Requested information from us or purchased goods or services from us; orIf you provided us with your details and ticked the box at the point of entry of your details for us to send you marketing communications; andIn each case, you have not opted out of receiving that marketing.We will not in any circumstances share your data with any third party for marketing purposes.You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by following the unsubscribe links on any marketing message sent to you or by visiting our website data portal or email marketing system and deleting or updating your profile.Where you opt out of receiving our marketing communications, this will not apply to personal data provided to us as a result of a product/service purchase, warranty registration, product/service experience or other transactions.CHANGE OF PURPOSEWe will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose.If we need to use your personal data for a purpose unrelated to the purpose for which we collected the data, we will notify you and we will explain the legal ground of processing.We may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent where this is required or permitted by law.DATA SECURITYWe have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know such data. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.DATA RETENTIONWe will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.THIRD-PARTY LINKSThis website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.COOKIESYou can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly.It is very important that the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date. Please let us know if at any time your personal information changes by emailing us at info@proboatclean.com.We use cookies to understand site usage through analytics and provide an excellent user experience. All data we collect is anonymised.When you visit a page with videos or social links, embedded from, for example, YouTube or Facebook, these third party service providers may set their own cookies. We do not control these so please check the third party websites for more information about these cookies.Where we use cookies.Statistics/Analytics
We use Google Analytics which helps us understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.Account related cookies
If you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies are usually deleted when you log out however in some cases they may remain to remember your site preferences when you next log in.Login related cookies
We use cookies when you are logged in to remember you are logged in this prevents you from having to log in again and again. These cookies are typically cleared when you log out for security purposes.Social Media
We also use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with your social network in various ways. For these to work these sites will set cookies through our site which may be used to enhance your profile on their site or contribute to the data they hold for various purposes outlined in their respective privacy policies.General NotesThe information generated by the cookie about your use of our sites (including your IP address which is anonymised) will be transmitted to and stored on servers in the United States.By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by those service providers in the manner and for the purposes set out above.We cannot control nor do we have access to any cookies placed on your computer by third party advertisers and sponsors.MANAGING YOUR DATAUpdating Account InformationYou may correct, amend or update profile or account information that is inaccurate at any time by emailing us at info@proboatclean.com.Deleting Information and AccountsYou may request that your account is deleted emailing us at info@proboatclean.com. News
KOOTENAYS FRANCHISE FOR SALE
Chris Wood is selling his Pro Boat Clean franchise in the Kootenays after 11 successful years. Currently based in Cranbrook,Find out More ...
Oxidised and dull boat deck – Before & After
Oxidised and dull boat deck before cleaningFind out More ...
More
In touchResourcesBoat Maintenance TipsPrivacy & Cookies Policy
© 2020 Proboat Clean All rights reserved.First Name:*Last Name:*Email*
We will use the data you submit to fulfil your request. Privacy Policy.
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
We use cookies to enhance your experience whilst on our site, and improve our services by analysing our site traffic we also use them to enable social media features.
By closing this banner, scrolling
or clicking a link or continuing to browse you agree to the use of cookies.AcceptRevoke cookiesCookie PolicyRevoke cookies
